we're going to talk to our newest
nightly show contributor hand gun thanks
for joining us uh Mr gun thank
you thank you Mr
gun Larry Please Mr gun's married to my
mother call me hand oh okay sorry uh
thanks an uh now I just wanted to get
your thoughts on this story about
allowing students to carry weapons on
campuses good idea or bad idea it's the
worst idea I've ever
heard okay and I've spent a fair amount
of time with some straight up murderers
Larry okay uh is that true have you seen
some action Larry my serial number was
rubbed off in ' 05 by a guy named baby
killer so yeah I've seen some
okay baby killer sounds pretty bad I
would agree with that so so and you're
worried about being on a college campus
yeah Larry listen guys like baby killer
live by a code okay I'm not saying I
agree with it but somebody does
something to him he does it back but
college kids man they're unpredictable
one minute I'm tucked away in a backpack
listening to him type up a psych paper
next thing you know he's on Molly and
I'm shooting up a frat
party I don't want to be that gun Larry
um now that that
uh that doesn't sound good well now what
about the safety of these students I
mean doesn't carrying a gun make people
safer oh God I hate when people say that
okay it doesn't even make sense Larry it
just makes me want to blow somebody's
head off
oh whoa I'm sorry I guess I just proved
my
point I wouldn't want to put me in the
hands of me Larry I'm designed to kill
man I understand well thanks for your
perspective hand you got it Larry love
the show by the most of the
time oh great job with the yesterday uh
it's a work in progress thanks hey
America follow the nightly show with
Larry Wilmore on Twitter but don't
follow me home I want followers but I
don't want followers that's stalking